pocketstarships.com 2017-07-17

# None

(Last Updated March 22, 2013)

Spectacle Games Inc. owns and operates the website located at www.spectaclegames.com (the Website) and creates Games which can be downloaded and played on PC, Mac Computers and Mobile Devices (the Games). These Privacy Policy and our Terms of Service Agreement (LINK) apply to all users of this website.

By registering for a Spectacle Account, using this site and/or any of Spectacle's online or mobile products and services, you agree to Spectacle's Privacy Policy and that we may transfer and store your information in the USA. You agree that Spectacle may process your data in accordance with the following privacy policy and that you will abide by Spectacle's Terms of Service.

IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THIS POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT USE ANY SPECTACLE SITE, ONLINE OR MOBILE PRODUCT OR SERVICE.

If we change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the home page or other places so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material or significant changes to this policy or the way we use your child's information, we will notify you or the parent/guardian here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page prior to the changes taking effect. Your continued use of our online and mobile products and services will signify your acceptance of the changes to our online Privacy Policy.

## Summary.

For your convenience, the following is a quick summary of our Privacy Policy. Please read the entire Privacy Policy for more detailed information. Spectacle Games collects both personal and nonpersonal consumer information. Personal information is information that identifies you and that can be used alone to contact to you. Nonpersonal information, alone, cannot be used to identify or contact you. When you use Spectacle Games Inc online and mobile products and services or you play our games on your PC or game system, we may collect certain nonpersonally identifiable information for purposes including improving our products and services, troubleshooting bugs, providing services to you, facilitating the provision of software updates, dynamically served content and product support as well as communicating with you. Spectacle Games Inc. collects nonpersonal information along with personal information when you actively provide it in the context of various online and mobile activities including online and mobile purchases, game registration and marketing surveys, for instance. In addition, we and other third parties use cookies and other technologies to passively collect nonpersonal demographic information, personalize your experience on our sites and monitor advertisements and other activities as described below. We may also derive from the information collected other facts, such as determining the applicable tax rate based on your IP address. 

**I. Personal Information**  
Registration for games  
Contest registration and prize acceptance  
Customer support and/or technical service requests  
Player match up and other headtohead  
online competitions Creation  
of a personal profile Product, service and subscribing to newsletters  
Service requests from third party service providers on our site and in game  
Access to our products and/or services on social networks or other third party services  
Otherwise through use of our software, mobile or online services where personal information is required for use and/or participation

**II. Nonpersonal Information**  
Cookies are small files applied to your Internet browser to track movements within websites. We may link cookie information to personal information. Cookies link to information regarding what items you have selected for purchase at our store, pages you have viewed, or games you have played. This information is used to keep track of your shopping cart and make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly, for example. Also, we use cookies to deliver content specific to your interest and to monitor website or game usage. We and third parties collect information on what games are played, howmuch time is spent playing the games and which ads or links are clicked.

If you disable cookies, you may lose some of the features and functionality of playing our games, as cookies are necessary to track and enhance your game activities. Please note that companies delivering advertisements in our games or on our websites may also use cookies or other technologies, and those practices are subject to their own policies. Please note that this privacy policy covers the use of cookies by Spectacle Games Inc. only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

Site tracking We use tracking software to monitor customer traffic patterns and site usage to help us develop the design and layout of the site to better meet the needs of visitors. This software does not enable us to capture any personally identifying information. Information collected will vary depending upon the activity and may include your name, email address, phone number, home address, birth date, mobile phone number and credit card information. Visitors to Spectacle Games Inc. Mobile may be asked to provide the name of their mobile service carrier, model of their mobile phone and a valid mobile number so that we may provide purchase instructions directly to their mobile phone. In that context, your mobile number will only be used to send you a text message with a link to download your game and will not be retained for any other purpose. Prize winners may be required to provide their Social Security or other identification number for tax purposes, and will be used only for prize fulfillment. We store your information using reasonable security precautions and for only as long as we think reasonably necessary. Despite such precautions, there is always a chance that someone may impermissible access your information. If you think a third party has accessed your information, please contact us immediately via support services. 

## Collection of Information

We do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to use our Service. If you are under 13, please do not send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. No one under the age of 13 may provide any personal information. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13, we will delete that information as quickly as possible.
